gsmserver.com 2013-12-08

# Privacy Policy

GsmServer understands that security and privacy are important issues for visitors of our web site and undertakes to keep your information secure and confidential. That is why we maintain the following standards to protect personal information. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice.

  * Collection of Information
  * Use of Information
  * Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
  * Protection of Information
  * Links to Other Websites
  * Access to Information

## Collection of Information

The information we learn from customers helps us to perform transactions, dispatch goods and provide customer support and continually improve your shopping experience at GsmServer online store. Here are the types of information we collect:

  * **Information you give us.** We receive and store any information you enter on our web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our service, and communicating with you. 
  * **Automatic information.** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. It includes the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, operating system, etc. This information is used for administration, analysis and website improvement. 
  * **Information from other sources.** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We can use updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties to correct our records and deliver your next purchase more quickly and communicate with you more easily.

## Use of Information

GsmServer uses your personal information for the following purposes: to process your orders and administer your account, to administer and improve the site and related services, to notify you of our products, services, promotional events or special offers that may interest you, etc.

## Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

Information about our customers is an important part of our business and we share customer information only as described below: 

  * **Third-party service providers.** We cooperate with other companies and individuals to deliver packages, send postal mail and e-mail, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service, etc. They have access to personal information required to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * **Protection of GsmServer.** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, protect the rights, property, or safety of GsmServer, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

## Security of Information

GsmServer is committed to protect customer personal information. 

  * We implement the following security measures: secure servers, firewalls and other technologies and procedures to protect customer personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.
  * We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

Please note! Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer in order to protect your account against unauthorized access.

## Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned by third parties. GsmServer is not responsible for the collection or use of your personal information at any third party sites. 

## Access to Information

You have an access to information about your account at GsmServer and you can view, update or delete it.
